Guide to the Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York Records and Photographs WAG.009
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series V: Addendum, 1957-2004
  - Subseries F: General Files, 1957-2004.
    - York College Chapter, 1995 (Box 190, Folder 15)
    - York College Chapter, 1996-2000 (Box 190, Folder 16)
    - York College Chapter: Grievances, 1980 (Box 190, Folder 17)
    - York College Chapter: Newsletter, 1974-1980 (Box 190, Folder 18)
    - Zeller, Belle, 1975-1991 (Box 190, Folder 19)
    - Zuccotti, John: New York City Deputy Mayor, 1976 (Box 190, Folder 20)
- Series VI: Legal Files, Arbitrations, and Grievances (CLOSED)
  - Grievances: A-Fab, 1970-1979 (Box 191)
  - Grievances: Fac-L.C., 1970-1979 (Box 192)
  - Grievances: Lea-Z, 1970-1979 (Box 193)
  - Legal Proceedings: Brown v. BHE, PSC v. BHE, London V. Polishook, Research Foundation v. Kinsella, 1975-1999 (Box 194)
  - Public Employment Relations Board, 1977-1990 (Box 195)
  - DNR: A-Bel (Box 196)
  - DNR: Ber-Bol (Box 197)
  - DNR: Bra-Clis (Box 198)
  - DNR: Cor-Esp (Box 199)
  - DNR: Etr-Gaa (Box 200)
  - DNR: Gat-Gro (Box 201)
  - DNR: Gru-Lac (Box 202)
  - DNR: Lah-Mos (Box 203)
  - DNR: N-Rec (Box 204)
  - DNR: Rin-Rod (Box 205)
  - DNR: Rog-Slo (Box 206)
  - DNR: Span-Tri (Box 207)
  - DNR: Tru-Zuc, miscellaneous (Box 208)
  - DNR: Workload: PSC v. Baruch-PSC v. MCC (Box 209)
  - DNR: Workload: PSC v. NYCC - PSC v. SICC, miscellaneous (Box 210)
  - DNR: Workload: Miscellaneous (Box 211)
- Series VII: Photographs and Audiovisual Materials, 1960s-1999
  Series VII: Photographs and Audiovisual Materials, contains photographs, negatives, and contact sheets related to faculty and PSC chapters at various campuses, as well as CUNY programs and administration, PSC affiliate groups, PSC officers, and PSC meetings and events. This series also includes some audiovisual materials.
  Arrangement
  Most of this series maintains the original arrangement of the photographs by Aaron Alexander, former Associate Executive Director of PSC.
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets, and Negatives re: Administration (CUNY), Admission Services (CUNY), Affiliate: AUP (American Association of University Professors, Affiliate: AFT (American Federation of Teachers), Affiliate: NYSUT (New York State United Teachers), Affiliate: UFT (United Federation of Teachers), Affiliate: United University Professions (SUNY), Alumni (CUNY), Arbitrators AAA, B.A. Program, Baruch College Faculty, Baruch NCSCBHEP, Baruch PSC Chapter, Board of Trustees- Board of Higher Education (CUNY), Bronx Community Faculty, and Bronx PSC Chapter, 1970s-1980s (Box 222)
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets, and Negatives re: Brooklyn College Faculty, Brooklyn College PSC Chapter, Brooklyn Educational Opportunity Center PSC Chapter, Career Counseling and Placement Assoc. (CUNY), Central Office Chapter, Chancellors Reception for Scholars/Distinguished Professors (CUNY), City College Faculty, City College NY-PSC Chapter, Computer Center (CUNY), Committee for Public Higher Education, Conferences- PSC, Delegate Assembly- PSC, Educational Opportunity Center (CUNY), Emergency Financial Control Board (CUNY), Faculty Development, Florida Chapter- PSC, General Equivalency Diploma (CUNY), Graduate School Faculty, and Graduate School PSC Chapter, 1970s-1980s (Box 223)
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets, and Negatives re: Graphics/ Cartoons, Higher Education Officers- PSC Chapter, History- PSC Chapter (1972-1980), History/Events- PSC, Hostos Community College, Hostos PSC Chapter, Hunter Campus Schools Chapter, and Hunter College Faculty, 1970s-1980s (Box 224)
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets, and Negatives re: Hunter PSC Chapter, Illustrative Photos (Students/Profs in Action), Instructional Resource Center (CUNY), John Jay College Faculty, John Jay PSC Chapter, Kingsborough Community Faculty, Kingsborough PSC Chapter, LaGuardia Community Faculty, LaGuardia PSC Chapter, Legislative Conference, Legislators/ Public Figures, Lehman College Faculty, and Lehman College PSC Chapter, 1970s-1980s (Box 225)
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets, and Negatives re: Library Association- PSC (LACUNY), Lobbying- PSC, Manhattan Community Faculty, Manhattan Community PSC Chapter, Manhattan Education Opportunity Center PSC Chapter, Medgar Evers Faculty, Medgar Evers PSC Chapter, Meetings- PSC, Miscellaneous- PSC, Miscellaneous Shots- Early Officers, Mystery Contacts and Negs., National Education Association, Negatives (1975), New York City, New York State, Personnel- PSC, Personnel- PSC (Adjunct Professors), and Personnel- PSC (Executive Council), 1970s-1980s (Box 226)
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets, and Negatives re: Personnel- PSC (Former Officers and Staff), Personnel- PSC (Grievance Counselors), Personnel- PSC (IHP), Personnel- PSC (Professional Staff), Personnel- PSC (Support Staff), Personnel- PSC (Welfare Fund), Private Colleges and Universities, Promotional Photographs, Public Figures, Queens College Chapter, Queens College Faculty, and Queensborough CC Faculty, 1970s-1980s (Box 227)
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets, and Negatives re: Queensborough CC PSC Chapter, Registrars PSC Chapter, Research Foundation PSC Chapter, Retirees PSC Chapter, Retirees PSC Chapter - Ed Daily, Staten Island College Faculty, Staten Island PSC Chapter, Technical College Faculty- NYC, Technical College PSC Chapter, University Student Center (CUNY), York College Faculty, York College PSC Chapter, Vorhees Tech. Inst. PSC Chapter, Retirees, Irwin Polishook, "Why Go to College?", United Federation of College Teachers, Beller Zeller Scholarship Fund, Arthur Kraus, and Unlabeled, 1960s-1980s (Box 228)
  - Six Cassette Tapes (three labeled "3 Radio Spots," two labeled "Neighborhood," and one labeled ":60 Radio 1) Neighborhood 2) Faculty") and Twenty-Three VHS Tapes ("Assembly Updates," "CUNY in Concert," "Jack Bigel with Victor Bigel," "Diversity In Education and NYSUT," "Jack Bigel with Walter Wriston," "Metroview: with Interim Chancellor," "NCSCBEP Conference -- Restoring Authority: Strong Presidents, Faculty Unions and Trustees," "NY 1 with Interim Chancellor," "Oral History- Jack Bigel and Barry Feinstein," "Oral History- Jack Bigel and Lewis Rudin," "PSCTV," "Science and the Written Word by Ronald Hoffman," "Voter Registration PSA," and "CUNY Voter Registration/Drop Out Rate"), 1992-1999 (Box 229)
  - Photographs of Belle Zeller, 1972 (Box OS 001)